Just when I thought, Hayato's voice
couldn't get any louder, he basically
broke the sound barrier today.
Ever since the sports festival,
Yota's been acting super weird.
He was normal happy go lucky Yota
during it...
KARAOKE
- Spacing out.
- But he's been completely out of it
lately.
And I've noticed Miki seems to be
avoiding him.
Did something happen between them
that day after school?
- Miki.
- What is it?
- You good?
- Huh?
Uh... Wh- why?
TWITCH...
She sucks at this.
I just didn't sleep well last night.
EEK
Oh. That's good to know.
Hmm.
Ever since the sports festival,
Miki's been acting super weird.
But up 'til then she'd been super
energetic.
I wonder why?
She's making that intense face again.
Did something happen between her and Yota
after cleanup?
Yota.
Koyun? What's wrong?
Uh. Well...
You good?
(SUPPOSED TO BE A) SMILE
BWAH
- She sucks at this.
- Uh.
Let's, uh... go outside.
Miki found out.
What? So- So does that mean...
Did you confess to her?
Nah.
I guess she just could kinda tell from
how I was acting.
It's my fault.
If I could've just been chill, she
wouldn't have found out, but part of me
maybe wanted her to?
For a split second, I let my mask slip
so maybe it'd get through to her.
Even though I wanted to keep things
as they were.
I'm so wishy-washy, aren't I?
Yeah, but everyone knows Miki thinks the
world of you.
If she clocked it, maybe she'll
pay attention now, and her
feelings might change.
Not gonna happen.
Since even back in junior high, Miki's
always just seen me as a friend.
A best friend, even.
Or I hope I am.
But... I was fine with that arrangement.
I really was.
I was convinced that I was, I dunno...
Okay, so she found out how you
feel about her.
Miki's not the kind of person who'd
hate you, or just cut you out of
her life, right?
She's just trying to figure out your
new dynamic.
Miki always treats everyone in her life
with care and respect.
She'd never do anything to hurt you.
Yeah.
That's why I think it's important I
don't leave things vague anymore.
Koyun. I...
I'm gonna end it properly.
Bombshell
I'm pretty sure Yota has feelings for me.
Which means, of course, I can't talk to
Minato or anybody else about it.
Whether it was all just in my head,
or even if it were actually true,
talking to someone about it would hurt
Yota really badly.
Oh no, and what about Koyun?
If Koyun likes Yota, then that means...
That my very existence would end up
hurting two people I care about.
Can I get the check please?
Ah! Thank you, come again!
Miki?
Did something happen again at school?
What?
You've really looked out of it all day.
Wait, really?
Sorry about that.
All right! Complain away!
Oh, no!
It's not that I need to vent.
But maybe it would be easier to
talk to them than my school friends.
Um.
If there was someone you'd only
ever thought of as a good friend,
and then you realized that friend,
they might have a- a crush on you...
What do you do when you find out?
Hmm.
Should you just pretend not to notice
and go back to how things were before?
Or should you just do your best to avoid
them?
I have no idea what to do now.
- How bittersweet.
Hm?
Honestly, if it were me, I'd probably
be flattered if it wasn't someone I
hated.
In fact, once I think a girl might
like me, I start to pay more
attention to her and then I tend to
fall for her right back.
Really?
Okay, but what if... if things don't go
well, then... then you'll have lost
the relationship and the friendship.
Oh.
I still out hang out with exes
all the time, it's not that big a deal.
Really? I can't even imagine that.
As you age, you'll have more
relationships that don't fit
- neatly in a box.
- Depends on who it is.
Is this friend of yours a girl?
- Or a guy?
- It's a guy friend.
Then I have absolutely no idea.
When it comes to one-sided, romantic
feelings from a person you can't beat
in one-on-one hand-to-hand combat, you
nip that in the bud before it grows.
Trust me here.
Taking a guy down is tough if you
don't have a weapon handy.
Jeez, what happened to you?
Look, a guy's fear of a spurned woman is
nothing compared to a woman's fear when
faced with a man she's rejected.
Uh, no.
He- He'd never fly into a rage, so
we're good on the hand-to-hand combat.
It'd probably be easiest if you just
grew to like him the way he likes you,
but...
The way he likes me...
Whenever I'm with Yota I always feel so...
Free to be myself.
And I have a blast.
And I bet Yota probably feels
the same way.
We give each other a warm, safe place
to belong.
Friends on equal footing.
But... are we really?
CAMERA ROLL
How would he have treated me if I wasn't
a girl?
If he didn't have a crush on me.
Would we have become remotely as
close as we are now?
Would he have still been as kind to me?
I don't want Yota to see me as a girl
or as a potential girlfriend.
I want him to see me as a person who
has value as a friend.
Hm?
INCOMING CALL
Minato?
What's up?
Nothin' much. You free to talk?
Yeah.
Hey, are you outside right now?
Mm-hm. I'm just walking Ponta.
Aw, my little Tanu-Poko?
It's Ponta, thank you very much.
- So what's up?
- It's nothing really.
I was just out on a walk and decided
I wanted to talk to someone.
That's all.
- What the heck, man?
- So, yeah.
Not really calling about anything in
particular.
There're just times when you kinda wanna
talk to someone, right?
Mm, I get that.
Although, uh, out of everyone else,
you called me?
- Why not?
- I dunno, it's just...
Don't you have a ton of girls blowing up
MEMORIES OF JUNIOR HIGH
your phone all the time?
Is that how you see me?
I don't have anyone like that.
And even if I did, I'd be considerate
and at least come up with a topic to
- call about first.
- But you don't need to do that with me?
Nah, you're different.
It's not like that with us.
Wait, what's with the pause?
Disappointed?
No, no way!
I know it's hard, but you'll get over me.
- Oh, shut your dumb mouth!
- Kidding.
Don't do that.
Jeez!
I'm outside right now too, and now I
look like a weirdo who's flipping out
in the bicycle parking lot.
You're just heading home?
- It's late.
- I was at work.
But I'm getting my bike now.
ZZZ...
Ponta's throwing in the towel,
so I should head home too.
Ponchiki...
It's Ponta.
- Well, see ya. Did I help you kill time?
- Yeah.
Thanks for that.
So you know, I'm here too if you need
to talk to someone.
- Okay.
- Anyway, see you at the after-party.
Oh, the cheer squad yakiniku thing!
Did you forget?
You better be there.
Yeah. You got it.
Have a good night.
I wonder how Miki actually feels about
Yota right now.
Does she see Yota just as a friend, like
how she sees Amamiya?
How long have you and Minato known each
other?
Minato, come on.
Do you think Yota and Minato are that
different?
Does she see him in that way?
Huh? Wait.
For Miki, Amamiya is...
And for Amamiya, Miki is...
A friend? Best friend?
Or maybe... something more?
And when it comes to me, how does he
see me?
Wait, no, who even cares about me right
now!?
Anyway, I hope they'll be able to
sort it out at the cheer squad
after-party tomorrow.
Good work at the festival, everyone!
Wow Miki, short hair looks so
good on you.
No, you never go with salt. You gotta
go with marinade.
- You think so?
- Totally. Maybe I'll cut mine too!
- It'd look so good on you!
- They didn't sort it out.
- Is it a hassle to style in the morning?
- Yeah.
Miki used to mainly just hang out with
guys, and usually only those in
- our grade.
- It can be sometimes.
Today she's talking only to the
upperclassmen.
Is it just cause it's a rare opportunity?
Am I overthinking it?
Yota hasn't even tried to move
from his seat all the way over there.
*IS NOT IN A POSITION TO TALK
- Stare...
- Hey, Koyuki, these're gonna burn!
- It was wild.
- Huh?
- Yeah, sounds like it.
- Wow, Amamiya's looking kinda cute today.
- I really had no idea.
- Have you really never heard of that?
- Ha, I said the same thing, man!
- Is it the glasses?
Oh, look at that.
Don't Momoka and Amamiya's outfits look
kinda similar?
Mm?
- Huh?
Stand side by side, you two!
Wow, you guys look good together.
- Thank you.
- Haha, such a flirt.
- Barf.
- Typical Minato.
Ah! Gosh, I'm kind of embarrassed.
Hm?
Don't act shy.
They'll end up just teasing you more.
Play along, and they'll get bored of it.
So smart.
Hey, you're pretty clever, aren't you?
PLAYING DUMB
- Am I?
- Aah. Adorable.
Come on, I'm hungry, let's eat!
Koyun.
SILENCE
Uh... Hey, Koyuki.
I always wondered but was scared to ask.
I was curious if you maybe disliked
Amamiya?
Huh? Wha- Why?
Well, just 'cause that's kind of the
vibe you were giving off.
No way, I don't. Uh, uh.
I really don't.
I don't, I- I swear.
That wasn't convincing.
Do I come across like I don't like him?
Hmm.
Well, you don't not seem like you
dislike him.
Then I'm giving the wrong impression.
- I'll have to work on that.
- Uh!
Don't go out of your way to change
anything.
Oh. Could I maybe sit with you?
Oh. Hey, Momoka!
Oh my gosh, my face is still flushing.
I'm embarrassed.
They can be so annoying, right?
Oh, I don't mind.
Actually, Amamiya's a great guy,
and I kind of like him.
- Hm!?
Huh? Is it really that surprising?
Wait. You mean like as in a romantic way?
Yeah. I'd say so.
Which is why I secretly liked it
when they said we looked good together.
Oh. Well, that's good.
Except Amamiya is...
Madame Koyun. What do you think?
Huh? About what?
Do you think it'd be okay for me to
give it a go?
I mean, that's...
That's your call to make.
It's not my place to say who you can or
can't date.
Oh, I'm so glad.
Because I was thinking, if you were
against it, then I wouldn't be
able to do anything about it.
Why are you asking me?
Huh? Because...
Well, if you were to reciprocate
his feelings, I wouldn't stand a
chance, would I?
His feelings?
- What do you...
- Oh no!
What? Come on.
- Are you just messing with me?
- Hm?
No, no, no, no!
Well, if you haven't figured it
out by now.
Amamiya clearly has a crush on you.
It's over...
Well, if you haven't figured it
out by now.
Amamiya clearly has a crush on you.
Uh.
Huh?
Y-You think Amamiya l- likes me?
Liar.
You're lying right now.
You have to be.
Madam Koyun.
There's no way you didn't know
Amamiya has feelings for you.
Don't tell me that you can't figure out
something as simple as "I think
he likes me?"
It's just that Amamiya is, well,
Amamiya's nice to everyone, so it's not
like I'm special or anything.
No.
Honestly, there are things that come to
mind.
But it's not a big deal.
I'm not special.
He's just friendly.
He's like that to everyone.
HEEHEE...
I told myself that.
I shoved it down, ignored it, because...
HOW WILL OUR RELATIONSHIP CHANGE?
WILL IT GET BETTER OR WORSE?
'Cause I was running away to protect
myself.
WHAT IF IT WAS ALL IN MY HEAD?
WHAT IF IT WASN'T ALL IN MY HEAD?
When, the whole time, in the back
of my mind, I think I was secretly
hoping "maybe".
But...
I didn't want her to be the one to
make me realize it.
Well, that's good.
Now I know I have nothing to worry about.
Wish me luck!
I'll try my hardest to get him to like me
back.
(NO COMMENT)
This girl's kinda scary.
I've changed my mind.
She doesn't give up.
Anyone still wanting to party, head down
to the river.
Okay, now let's see...
- My shoes...
- Hmp.
Oh. Yours was next to mine?
Yeah.
Whoa! Aah!
Wait.
- Huh? Hm?
- Koyun.
Look, we're twins!
STIFF STIFF
Huh?
Ah! Oh no!
He's gonna get the wrong impression.
Quickly, say something back!
Ah! Yeah, it was super cheap, wasn't it?
Yeah, I know.
But I liked that it looked expensive.
I thought the same thing.
It'll be our secret.
I won't tell if you won't.
How 'bout it?
My glasses are cheap too, by the way.
Good to know.
Ah... What do I do...?
If I told, they'd find out about
mine too.
Man, this is so much fun.
I wanna stay exactly as we are now, at
this distance, forever.
Thank goodness! That was a close one!
I almost thought I'd lost the key for my
shoes.
Back it up.
You can't go this way.
What? Huh? Why?
You gonna watch the fireworks?
Yeah.
- Miki and Tsukiko are gonna go too.
- Oh, that's good.
We didn't get much of a chance to talk
today, so I hoped you'd be there.
If I wasn't sure before, I think
it's safe to say it's pretty clear now.
Wait. What do I do?
What do I do? What do I do?
O-Oh.
That's cool.
Koyun! Where are you?
Right here!
ALL ALONE
Lift it higher.
Hey! C'mon, get down here.
I'm good. I'm just gonna watch from here.
You're so full of it. You just can't get
down!
You can do it! See!
- Here!
- What the-!
HEIGHT
I'm scared!
Put me down!
Okay, okay, one sec.
Aaahhh!
What was that?
What's up!
If it isn't Koyun, Yota, and Lil Tsukiko!
Yuki, did you hear that weird scream
just now?
Oh, that?
That was Atagawa.
She seems like really angry.
Isn't it too early to do senko sparklers?
You save those for the end.
Hmph.
You can do them whenever you want, alright?
- Yeah, true that.
- You wanna do one?
You bet I do.
- Stare...
- How did I end up in this position?
IN THE MIDDLE
I feel her eyes boring into my soul.
Aw. It fell.
I'm gonna make yours fall too.
BLOW
Knock it off.
- Huh?
Mind if I join you all?
Huh?
- Can I?
- Huh?
- Whoa, what's wrong?
- Uh...
THUMP THUMP THUMP THUMP
- This is interesting...
What's with these faces?
CRACKLE CRACKLE
BLAST
- Amazing!
- Oh, look at 'em go!
Oh, it's like from a movie!
Oh, I could cry.
Well, it's just so pretty!
Wanna see which one of us lasts longer?
Mm-hm.
Our elbows are so close.
Oh, it lit.
Uh.
Smile...
SMILE
STIFF STIFF
Yeah! This is awesome!
- Congrats, everyone, on a good sports
- festival!
- We did it!
- Oh my gosh, that was so much fun!
Miki.
This is yours, right?
I guess it fell.
Huh? Wait, what?
That's my key chain.
You're right. It must've fallen off.
- Here.
- Oh, er, thanks.
Although how did you know it was mine?
Hmm. How could I not know?
Miki, is it awkward being around me?
What?
You're just so easy to read.
No. It's not...
That's not it.
- I'm sorry.
- Huh?
If you have a minute, can we maybe talk?
There's something I wanted to bring up.
Miki.
If he doesn't say what he's about to say,
then things can stay as they are.
I like you.
Huh? What?
Thank you!
Oh... He's...
Serious.
It's not a joke.
Or messing around. He really means it.
Since we were in junior high, I've had
feelings for you.
What? You've had feelings that long?
F-for me?
If I'm being honest, I never planned on
telling you.
But I sucked at hiding it.
So I wanted to make it right.
I need to close that door.
So that way we can just be friends again.
And I'm sorry. Truly.
Yota always has a smile on his face,
but this face is one I've never seen.
Why am I doing this?
Why am I stealing Yota's smile from him?
Because in the end, I like Yota, too.
I even love him.
But only in a...
No.
Maybe if- if I start trying to see
him in that way, my feelings might
change.
I mean, is there anybody else
in the world who would accept me
and love me like this, just the way I am?
If I could love the person who loves me,
love him back the way he does...
I know I'd definitely be happy.
Yota.
But then again.
I'm so sorry.
With these feelings I have...
It's not that- that I don't like you.
I can't reciprocate.
But I just honestly never thought of
you that way.
Mm-hm.
And I just didn't know what to do.
Yeah. I understand.
I'm sorry... For avoiding you and stuff.
I never meant to hurt you or anything.
Yeah. I know, Miki.
Sorry.
Thank you.
C'mon, why are you crying?